tubetamil.com 2018-06-13

# TubeTamil Privacy Notice | Tubetamil.com

[tubetamil.com](http://www.tubetamil.com/) welcomes you. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it.

From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy. We will endeavor to post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of the privacy policy will appear at the top of this page. This consumer privacy policy applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source.

## Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies

Like many websites, and web and mobile services, we may use (or work with third party partners who use) a variety of technologies to learn more about how people interact with our Services. This section provides more information about some of those technologies and how they work.

**Cookies** : Cookies are small files that websites and other online services use to store information about users on the users’ own computers. Cookies can be used to store sign-in credentials so that you don’t have to enter them each time you return to a website, or to store other information to make web viewing more customized or efficient upon future visits. Cookies also may store a unique identifier tied to your computer so that web services and advertising networks can recognize you across visits to different websites. You can configure your Internet browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse all or certain cookies completely.

We (or our partners) may use or support cookies for purposes including the following:

  *     * To collect information about your browsing activities in order to deliver customized or relevant services, advertising or content to you (including regarding our own products and content), when you browse our Website or other websites or open the emails we send you;

  *     * To relate the information collected by cookies to information we obtain from you directly or from commercially available sources;

  *     * To work with third parties that serve advertisements (through our Services or across the Internet) or provide other services to us, such as providing users the ability to comment on content, allowing users to share content, or tracking website usage statistics. We do not control these third party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies. For more information about third party ad networks and services that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), and to learn about or exercise your opt-out options, go to <http://aboutads.info/choices>. To learn more about how third parties may collect and use information online, and how you can exercise opt-out choices regarding that information, see the below Section titled “[Information Collected by Third-Parties and Your Ad & Cookie Choices](http://www.tubetamil.com/tubetamil-privacy-notice).”

  *     * **Other Local Storage**  We (or our partners) may use other kinds of local storage, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as “Flash cookies”) and HTML5 local storage, in connection with the Services. These technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your computer and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these objects are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies. Your browser may allow you to disable its HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in its HTML5 local storage. For information about deleting information contained in Local Shared Objects or adjusting related preferences

  * **Web Beacons**  We (or our partners) may use technologies called web beacons that communicate information from your Internet browser to a web server. Web beacons can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, and can allow a web server to read certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the web beacon, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the web beacon was viewed. These web beacons may be used for a variety of purposes, including to analyze the use of the Services and in conjunction with cookies to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you.

**Tubetamil.com works with third parties, including advertising companies and website analytics firms, who use cookies to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) when you visit our Site and third party sites. This Non-PII, collected through cookies, is typically used by these third party advertising networks to serve you advertisements tailored to meet your preferences and likely interests, while on third party sites. If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out, or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies.**

  *     * For more information about these third-party Ad Networks and opting out of tracking through the NAI, visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

  *     * For more information about interest-based advertising and opting out through the DAA, visit: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

  *     * For more information about disabling and controlling third-party cookies in your browser, visit: <http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1>

  * For more information on nRelate and opting out of browser history tracking

## Legitimate Interest

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy ](http://exponential.com/privacy/)or contact their data protection officer via [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## With whom we share your information:

We do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this privacy policy. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission. We may share (provide and receive) with others certain aggregate service information, which is not personally identifiable. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes.

## Communications with Us:

We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contacting us with a question or problem related to the service). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

## Links:

We may display links to other sites within TubeTamil.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

## Downloads:

We do link to other web sites which might support download. We are not responsible for the downloadable materials that are present in these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding the downloadable materials of these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding these downloads in the websites that our visitors refer to in our forums and discussions. Downloads referred to in this privacy policy can be videos, images, software, games and any application files.

More Information  
For questions concerning the product or your account, please. For more  
information about our privacy practices, write to us at:[  
[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2c58594e49584d4145406c444358414d4540024f4341)
